Hello friends welcome to my channel so
friends in today's video I am going to
show you the full review of the TVS Ryder vehicle,
above the tank so
friends you can see right now it means
we can show you friends you can see
here you will find your tank which you can see
how the tank looks to you
friends it will look very good
friends the entire panel on top means it has
come out friends you can see all the
panels in front of you after that you will have to
open all the keys to put it
inside
friends so let's show you
what is inside friends you will get the tin
from above and that means
plastic it will look very good meaning
friends you can see it very well it has been tightened
with the help of screws
friends there is no problem for you in this
many people say that it will break
friends there is nothing like that the vehicle means it will
fall something means it will break nothing will happen
friends you can see
inside means only the final one has been fitted
you will get whatever is inside it
friends we are showing you you
can see friends this is your entire tank
Because it is covered from the top which is a
very good look, from the top friends it is
very strong, that means this tank
gives it, friends it gives fiber only on the top
but inside it is very
tough, that means it gives it to you with great strength.